What's wrong with you?
You're like the worst wingman ever.
Are you kidding me, Chelsea?
I'm an incredible wingman.
I know, but, like, nothing?
It's just harder than you think with him.
Like, what about a blowjob?
I'm good right now, but thank you.
Maybe in, like, 10 minutes?
Maybe after this beer?
Sorry, I'm just making a mental list
of all the things I'd like to do
before giving you a blowjob.
Wow. Really?
Kill myself is number one.
Are you serious? Jesus. What's number two?
Just, like, awaiting trial in Guantanamo.
"Yup.
- Yeah.
Come on, man. The blues?
Are you fucking serious?
What the fuck does Captain Attractive
have to be so sad about?
I don't know.
I think he's going
for brooding and dark, mysterious.
It's kind of working for me.
- That is working?
- Yes.
You cannot be that attractive
and have a skill. That's bullshit.
Well, I'm gonna play, so you're wrong.
Then somebody's in trouble.
Cheer up, asshole. You're the guy.
Buckle up.
Hey, excuse me?
I just wanted to tell you great job.
I almost cried right there.
It was really some powerful stuff.
Yeah. It was brooding, dark,
and mysterious, apparently.
- Yeah.
- Thanks. That's what I was going for.
Told you.
This is my friend, Chelsea.
She's not much to look at,
but wait till you hear her play the piano.
- Really good.
- I can't wait. I'm Diego.
I know you are.
I warn you, though.
She can be really aggressive sometimes.
Is that right?
But you can tame her with tequila
and compliments.
- Yeah.
- So...
- Super aggressive.
- Yeah?
- Hey, are you home?
- No. I'm at the hospital. Where are you?
I'm headed back.
All right. So?
How was it?
It was amazing, man. She was amazing.
So is she coming back to the house or what?
Not exactly.
- Hey.
- After midnight? Really?
I couldn't sleep.
It's good to see you.
So what happened with you
and the piano man? Rodrigo?
- Diego?
- Diego.
I don't know.
I don't want to date a guy
that's prettier than me. You know?
Yeah. Me neither.
Plus, he works out.
I don't want a man that works out.
Yeah. I worked out once. 2004.
Got on the 15 dumbbells.
I was like, "Those are way too light,
let me go to the 30s."
- Nice.
- And if you feel it...
Don't. I don't wanna touch it.
And then I hit the hammies.
- Some quads. And if you feel that.
- You definitely got the lingo down.
- Do you see that?
- No.
- Well...
- Fat.
That's what happens when you work out
once.
What are you doing here anyway?
- What do you mean?
- I don't know.
Weren't you supposed to hang out
with that girl from Trinity?
Yeah. I had to tell her
I wasn't looking for anything too serious.
'Cause if it ever stopped being fun for you
guys, you'd want to just call it off?
- That's... Yeah.
- I know.
You got it down.
- Brother. I know the spiel.
- Brother.
Yeah.
I don't know. I just thought you liked her.
I did like her.
She was cool, really smart, funny, well-read.
- Great family.
- Love it.
And gave the best blowjob
in recorded history.
I feel like every blowjob you get,
you think is the best in recorded history...
Well, if you look at the common variable
across all encounters, you'll find that it's me.
So maybe I'm the best in recorded history
at receiving blowjobs.
- Bam.
- Think about that.
- Don't want to.
Cheers to me getting awesome blowjobs
and just being good at it.
You're such an idiot.